import '../../presentation/widget/quiz_questions_widget.dart';

Map<String, dynamic> chemPathQuestion = {
  'Amatuer': <QuizQuestionsWidget>[],
  'Easy': <QuizQuestionsWidget>[
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which of the following is a primary function of chemical pathology laboratory?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Diagnosis and monitoring of disease',
        'Surgical procedure',
        'X-ray imaging',
        'Physiotherapy'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Diagnosis and monitoring of disease',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which organ is primarily responsible for metabolizing drugs and toxins in the body?',
      quizOptions: const ['Kidneys', 'Liver', 'Heart', 'Lungs'],
      correctOption: 'Liver',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion: 'What is the main function of the kidneys?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Regulation of blood sugar levels',
        'Regulation of blood pressure',
        'Filtering waste products from the blood and producing urine',
        'Production of digestive enzymes'
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Filtering waste products from the blood and producing urine',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which of the following is a common electrolyte found in the blood?',
      quizOptions: const ['Vitamin C', 'Sodium', 'Vitamin D', 'Vitamin K'],
      correctOption: 'Sodium',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion: 'What is the normal pH range of human blood?',
      quizOptions: const ['0-7', '7-14', '6-8', '7.35-7.45'],
      correctOption: '7.35-7.45',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which hormone is responsible for regulating blood glucose levels?',
      quizOptions: const ['Insulin', 'Estrogen', 'Testosterone', 'Thyroxine'],
      correctOption: 'Insulin',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion: 'What is the main function of cholesterol in the body?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Regulates blood pressure',
        'Provides energy',
        'Forms cell membranes and is a precursor to steroid hormones',
        'Aids in digestion'
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Forms cell membranes and is a precursor to\n steroid hormones',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion: 'Which of the following is a liver function test?',
      quizOptions: const ['Troponin', 'Creatinine', 'Bilirubin', 'Hemoglobin'],
      correctOption: 'Bilirubin',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion: 'Which enzyme is commonly elevated in liver damage?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Amylase',
        'Lipase',
        'Alanine aminotransferase (ALT)',
        'Creatine kinase (CK)'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Alanine aminotransferase (ALT)',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'What is the normal range for fasting blood glucose levels?',
      quizOptions: const [
        '2.5-4.0 mmol/L',
        '5.0-7.0 mmol/L',
        '8.0-10.0 mmol/L',
        '3.9-5.6 mmol/L'
      ],
      correctOption: '3.9-5.6 mmol/L',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which of the following is a common marker for kidney function?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Troponin',
        'Urea',
        'Alanine aminotransferase (ALT)',
        'C-reactive protein (CRP)'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Urea',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion: 'What does LDL stand for in relation to cholesterol?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Low Density Lipoprotein',
        'High Density Lipoprotein',
        'Light Density Lipoprotein',
        'Large Diameter Lipoprotein'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Low Density Lipoprotein',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which of the following is a function of electrolytes in the body?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Regulating blood pressure',
        'Providing energy',
        'Aiding in digestion',
        'Forming cell membranes'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Regulating blood pressure',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion: 'What is the primary function of the thyroid gland?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Regulating calcium levels',
        'Regulating blood sugar levels',
        'Regulating metabolism',
        'Regulating blood pressure'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Regulating metabolism',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which of the following is an indicator of kidney function?',
      quizOptions: const ['Glucose', 'Creatinine', 'Triglycerides', 'Troponin'],
      correctOption: 'Creatinine',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which of the following is a lipid molecule found in cell membranes and used as a precursor for steroid hormones?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Triglyceride',
        'Cholesterol',
        'Glucose',
        'Creatinine'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Cholesterol',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion: 'What is the primary function of the pancreas?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Producing insulin and glucagon to regulate blood sugar levels',
        'Filtering waste products from the blood',
        'Producing bile to aid in digestion',
        'Regulating blood pressure'
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Producing insulin and glucagon to regulate blood sugar levels',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which of the following is a common marker for inflammation in the body?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Troponin',
        'C-reactive protein (CRP)',
        'Urea',
        'Amylase'
      ],
      correctOption: 'C-reactive protein (CRP)',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'What is the normal range for total cholesterol levels in the blood?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Less than 3.0 mmol/L',
        '3.0-5.0 mmol/L',
        '5.0-7.0 mmol/L',
        'Less than 10.0 mmol/L'
      ],
      correctOption: '3.0-5.0 mmol/L',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion: 'Which of the following is a function of hemoglobin?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Regulating blood pressure',
        'Carrying oxygen to tissues',
        'Aiding in digestion',
        'Regulating blood sugar levels'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Carrying oxygen to tissues',
    ),
  ],
  'Hard': <QuizQuestionsWidget>[
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A 50-year-old female patient with fatigue, weight gain, and cold intolerance presents with a TSH level of 8.5 mIU/L and a free thyroxine (T4) level of 0.8 ng/dL. What condition do these lab results suggest?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Hypothyroidism',
        'Hyperthyroidism',
        'Thyroiditis',
        'Euthyroid sick syndrome'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Hypothyroidism',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A 30-year-old male patient with jaundice, abdominal pain, and dark urine has a serum bilirubin level of 3.5 mg/dL and liver enzyme levels (AST and ALT) of 200 U/L and 180 U/L, respectively. What condition do these lab results suggest?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Cholecystitis',
        'Liver cirrhosis',
        'Hepatitis',
        'Gallstones'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Hepatitis',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A 45-year-old female patient with muscle weakness, bone pain, and frequent fractures shows a serum calcium level of 7.5 mg/dL and a serum phosphate level of 6.0 mg/dL. What condition do these lab results suggest?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Hypercalcemia',
        'Hypocalcemia',
        'Hyperphosphatemia',
        'Hypophosphatemia'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Hypocalcemia',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A 60-year-old male patient with abdominal distension, pedal edema, and fatigue has a serum albumin level of 2.5 g/dL and a serum bilirubin level of 2.0 mg/dL. What condition do these lab results suggest?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Nephrotic syndrome',
        'Liver cirrhosis',
        'Chronic kidney disease',
        'Congestive heart failure'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Liver cirrhosis',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A 35-year-old female patient with recurrent urinary tract infections and flank pain presents with a serum creatinine level of 2.0 mg/dL and a decreased glomerular filtration rate (GFR) of 40 mL/min/1.73m^2. What condition do these lab results suggest?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Acute kidney injury',
        'Chronic kidney disease',
        'Nephrotic syndrome',
        'Urinary tract obstruction'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Chronic kidney disease',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A 55-year-old male patient with chest pain, shortness of breath, and fatigue shows cardiac biomarker levels of troponin at 2.5 ng/mL and CK-MB at 100 U/L. What condition do these lab results suggest?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Myocardial infarction',
        'Heart failure',
        'Pericarditis',
        'Angina pectoris'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Myocardial infarction',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A 70-year-old female patient with confusion, nausea, and muscle weakness has a serum calcium level of 13 mg/dL. What condition do these lab results suggest?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Hypercalcemia',
        'Hypocalcemia',
        'Hyperkalemia',
        'Hypokalemia'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Hypercalcemia',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A 25-year-old male patient with joint pain, rash, and fatigue presents with rheumatoid factor levels of 100 IU/mL and anti-cyclic citrullinated peptide (anti-CCP) antibody levels of 80 U/mL. What condition do these lab results suggest?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Rheumatoid arthritis',
        'Systemic lupus erythematosus',
        'Sjögren\'s syndrome',
        'Psoriatic arthritis'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Rheumatoid arthritis',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A 40-year-old female patient with polyuria, polydipsia, and weight loss shows fasting blood glucose levels of 250 mg/dL and an HbA1c level of 10%. What condition do these lab results suggest?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Type 1 diabetes mellitus',
        'Type 2 diabetes mellitus',
        'Gestational diabetes',
        'Impaired glucose tolerance'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Type 2 diabetes mellitus',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A 65-year-old male patient with chest pain, palpitations, and dyspnea has brain natriuretic peptide (BNP) levels at 800 pg/mL and troponin levels at 3.0 ng/mL. What condition do these lab results suggest?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Congestive heart failure',
        'Myocardial infarction',
        'Pulmonary embolism',
        'Atrial fibrillation'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Congestive heart failure',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A 50-year-old female patient with abdominal pain, diarrhea, and weight loss shows tissue transglutaminase (tTG) antibody levels at 80 U/mL. What condition do these lab results suggest?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Celiac disease',
        'Crohn\'s disease',
        'Ulcerative colitis',
        'Irritable bowel syndrome'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Celiac disease',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A 30-year-old male patient with excessive thirst, frequent urination, and blurred vision has urine ketone levels at 4+ and blood glucose levels at 400 mg/dL. What condition do these lab results suggest?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Diabetic ketoacidosis',
        'Hyperosmolar hyperglycemic state',
        'Type 1 diabetes mellitus',
        'Type 2 diabetes mellitus'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Diabetic ketoacidosis',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A 55-year-old female patient with excessive hair growth, acne, and irregular menstrual periods presents with serum testosterone levels at 150 ng/dL. What condition do these lab results suggest?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Polycystic ovary syndrome (PCOS)',
        'Cushing\'s syndrome',
        'Ovarian tumor',
        'Hyperthyroidism'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Polycystic ovary syndrome (PCOS)',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A 45-year-old male patient with weakness, fatigue, and pale skin shows serum hemoglobin levels at 8 g/dL and hematocrit levels at 25%. What condition do these lab results suggest?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Iron deficiency anemia',
        'Vitamin B12 deficiency anemia',
        'Aplastic anemia',
        'Hemolytic anemia'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Iron deficiency anemia',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A 60-year-old female patient with muscle cramps, tingling sensations, and arrhythmias has serum potassium levels at 6.5 mmol/L. What condition do these lab results suggest?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Hyperkalemia',
        'Hypokalemia',
        'Hypercalcemia',
        'Hypocalcemia'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Hyperkalemia',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A 60-year-old male patient presents with rectal bleeding, change in bowel habits, and unintentional weight loss. Colonoscopy reveals a mass in the colon, and his carcinoembryonic antigen (CEA) level is 7 ng/mL. What condition do these lab results suggest?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Colorectal cancer',
        'Hemorrhoids',
        'Inflammatory bowel disease',
        'Diverticulitis'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Colorectal cancer',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A 55-year-old female patient with a family history of breast cancer notices a painless lump in her breast. Mammography confirms the presence of a mass, and her serum levels of cancer antigen 15-3 (CA 15-3) are 35 U/mL. What condition do these lab results suggest?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Breast cancer',
        'Fibroadenoma',
        'Mastitis',
        'Cystic breast disease'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Breast cancer',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A 70-year-old male patient presents with dysphagia, weight loss, and regurgitation of food. Endoscopy reveals a mass in the esophagus, and his serum levels of squamous cell carcinoma antigen (SCC-Ag) are 4 ng/mL. What condition do these lab results suggest?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Esophageal cancer',
        'Gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD)',
        'Esophageal stricture',
        'Barrett\'s esophagus'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Esophageal cancer',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A 50-year-old male smoker presents with a chronic cough, hemoptysis, and chest pain. Chest X-ray reveals a lung mass, and his serum levels of neuron-specific enolase (NSE) are 25 ng/mL. What condition do these lab results suggest?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Lung cancer',
        'Chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD)',
        'Pneumonia',
        'Tuberculosis'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Lung cancer',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A 65-year-old female patient presents with abdominal pain, bloating, and early satiety. Imaging studies show ovarian masses, and her serum levels of cancer antigen 125 (CA 125) are 80 U/mL. What condition do these lab results suggest?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Ovarian cancer',
        'Ovarian cysts',
        'Endometriosis',
        'Pelvic inflammatory disease (PID)'
      ],
      correctOption: 'Ovarian cancer',
    ),
  ],
  'Professional': <QuizQuestionsWidget>[
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A chemical pathology lab introduces a new automated analyzer for measuring blood glucose levels. After implementation, the lab notices discrepancies between the results obtained from the new analyzer and the reference method. What steps should the lab take to identify and address these discrepancies according to ISO 15189 standards?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Perform method comparison studies, calibrate the new analyzer, and implement corrective actions.',
        'Continue using the new analyzer without changes.',
        'Discontinue using the new analyzer and revert to the reference method.',
        'Ignore the discrepancies and proceed with testing as usual.'
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Perform method comparison studies, calibrate the new analyzer, and implement corrective actions.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'During routine quality control checks, a chemical pathology lab discovers that one of its reagents has exceeded its expiration date. The lab has already used this reagent in multiple patient tests. What actions should the lab take to assess the impact on patient results and ensure compliance with ISO 15189 requirements?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Continue using the expired reagent as it may still be effective.',
        'Stop using the expired reagent and discard any remaining stock.',
        'Retest all patient samples using a different reagent.',
        'Perform a risk assessment, document the impact on patient results, and take appropriate corrective actions.'
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Perform a risk assessment, document the impact on patient results, and take appropriate corrective actions.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A chemical pathology lab receives a complaint from a healthcare provider regarding incorrect test results for a patient. Upon investigation, the lab identifies a clerical error in data entry during result reporting. How should the lab document and address this incident within its quality management system framework in accordance with ISO 15189 standards?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Ignore the clerical error as it does not affect patient care.',
        'Document the incident and inform the healthcare provider of the error.',
        'Modify patient records to correct the error.',
        'Implement measures to prevent similar errors in the future and document the corrective actions taken.'
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Implement measures to prevent similar errors in the future and document the corrective actions taken.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'The quality control data for a specific test in a chemical pathology lab consistently falls outside the acceptable range over several days. Despite troubleshooting efforts, the cause of the deviation remains unidentified. What steps should the lab take to further investigate and resolve this issue in accordance with ISO 15189 guidelines?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Ignore the deviations as they may be due to random variation.',
        'Discontinue the test and rely on alternative methods.',
        'Conduct a root cause analysis, implement corrective actions, and monitor the effectiveness of the interventions.',
        'Continue testing without taking any further action.'
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Conduct a root cause analysis, implement corrective actions, and monitor the effectiveness of the interventions.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A chemical pathology lab is preparing for an external audit by a regulatory agency. As part of the audit preparation, the lab must ensure compliance with accreditation requirements related to quality management systems. What documentation and processes should the lab prioritize to demonstrate adherence to ISO 15189 standards during the audit?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Provide evidence of staff training and competency assessments, maintain accurate records of quality control data, and demonstrate adherence to standard operating procedures.',
        'Hide any non-conformities to avoid scrutiny during the audit.',
        'Refuse the audit as the lab is already compliant with ISO 15189.',
        'Document fabricated data to create the appearance of compliance.'
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Provide evidence of staff training and competency assessments, maintain accurate records of quality control data, and demonstrate adherence to standard operating procedures.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Following the implementation of a new testing procedure in a chemical pathology lab, staff members report difficulty in following the updated protocols. How should the lab address this issue within its quality management system framework, considering ISO 15189 recommendations for training and competency?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Ignore staff concerns and proceed with the new procedure.',
        'Provide additional training and support to staff members to ensure competency in the new procedure.',
        'Discontinue the new procedure and revert to the previous method.',
        'Punish staff members for reporting difficulties with the new procedure.'
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Provide additional training and support to staff members to ensure competency in the new procedure.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A chemical pathology lab experiences a power outage during a critical testing period, resulting in the loss of refrigerated samples. How should the lab document and manage this incident according to ISO 15189 guidelines for risk management and contingency planning?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Ignore the incident as it was beyond the lab\'s control.',
        'Document the incident, assess the impact on sample integrity, and implement measures to prevent similar incidents in the future.',
        'Hide the incident to avoid repercussions.',
        'Discard all affected samples without investigation.'
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Document the incident, assess the impact on sample integrity, and implement measures to prevent similar incidents in the future.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'The laboratory director of a chemical pathology lab decides to update the lab\'s quality management system to align with ISO 15189 requirements. What steps should the lab take to ensure a successful transition and implementation of the new standards?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Ignore the new standards and continue with the existing quality management system.',
        'Develop a transition plan, provide staff training on the new requirements, and update documentation and procedures accordingly.',
        'Resist the changes and refuse to implement the new standards.',
        'Implement the new standards without informing staff members.'
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Develop a transition plan, provide staff training on the new requirements, and update documentation and procedures accordingly.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'During an internal audit of a chemical pathology lab, a non-conformity is identified related to equipment calibration records. How should the lab address this non-conformity in accordance with ISO 15189 guidelines for corrective and preventive actions?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Ignore the non-conformity as it is not important.',
        'Document the non-conformity, investigate the root cause, and implement corrective actions to prevent recurrence.',
        'Conceal the non-conformity to avoid negative consequences.',
        'Continue using the equipment without calibration.'
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Document the non-conformity, investigate the root cause, and implement corrective actions to prevent recurrence.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A chemical pathology lab receives a shipment of new laboratory equipment. What procedures should the lab follow to ensure proper installation, validation, and calibration of the equipment, as recommended by ISO 15189 standards?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Skip installation and calibration to save time.',
        'Install the equipment without validation or calibration.',
        'Follow manufacturer\'s instructions for installation, perform validation studies to ensure accuracy and precision, and calibrate the equipment according to established protocols.',
        'Install the equipment without consulting manufacturer\'s instructions.'
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Follow manufacturer\'s instructions for installation, perform validation studies to ensure accuracy and precision, and calibrate the equipment according to established protocols.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A chemical pathology lab conducts regular proficiency testing to assess the accuracy and reliability of its test results. How should the lab analyze and respond to proficiency testing results in accordance with ISO 15189 requirements?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Ignore proficiency testing results as they do not accurately reflect lab performance.',
        'Analyze proficiency testing results, identify areas for improvement, and implement corrective actions to address any deficiencies.',
        'Fabricate proficiency testing results to maintain the appearance of compliance.',
        'Discontinue participation in proficiency testing to save costs.'
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Analyze proficiency testing results, identify areas for improvement, and implement corrective actions to address any deficiencies.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'The quality manager of a chemical pathology lab is tasked with developing a quality manual that outlines the lab\'s quality management system according to ISO 15189 standards. What key components should be included in the quality manual to ensure compliance with the requirements?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Detailed procedures for every test performed in the lab.',
        'Organizational structure, scope of activities, quality policy, and procedures for document control, internal audit, and corrective actions.',
        'Blank pages to fill in as needed.',
        'Irrelevant information to confuse auditors.'
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Organizational structure, scope of activities, quality policy, and procedures for document control, internal audit, and corrective actions.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A chemical pathology lab introduces a new testing methodology for a specific assay. What validation studies should the lab perform to ensure the accuracy, precision, and reliability of the new methodology, as recommended by ISO 15189 guidelines?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Skip validation studies to expedite implementation.',
        'Perform analytical sensitivity studies only.',
        'Conduct validation studies including accuracy, precision, analytical sensitivity, analytical specificity, and reference intervals.',
        'Ignore validation studies as they are unnecessary.'
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Conduct validation studies including accuracy, precision, analytical sensitivity, analytical specificity, and reference intervals.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Following a change in laboratory personnel, a chemical pathology lab identifies a need for additional training to ensure staff competency. How should the lab develop and implement a training program that meets the requirements of ISO 15189 standards?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Provide training only to selected staff members.',
        'Develop a comprehensive training program based on identified training needs, ensure staff participation, and document training records.',
        'Provide minimal training to save costs.',
        'Conduct training sessions without documentation.'
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Develop a comprehensive training program based on identified training needs, ensure staff participation, and document training records.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A chemical pathology lab conducts regular internal audits to assess the effectiveness of its quality management system. How should the lab plan, conduct, and document internal audits in accordance with ISO 15189 guidelines?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Conduct audits sporadically without planning or documentation.',
        'Plan and schedule audits, conduct audits using trained auditors, document audit findings, and implement corrective actions as needed.',
        'Avoid internal audits to prevent uncovering non-conformities.',
        'Conduct audits only when external auditors are present.'
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Plan and schedule audits, conduct audits using trained auditors, document audit findings, and implement corrective actions as needed.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A chemical pathology lab experiences a sudden increase in test volume due to a public health outbreak. How should the lab manage the increased workload while maintaining the quality and reliability of test results, as outlined in ISO 15189 standards for laboratory operations?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Increase turnaround time and prioritize urgent samples over routine ones.',
        'Hire untrained staff to meet the demand.',
        'Discontinue certain tests to focus on others.',
        'Implement measures such as additional shifts, staff training, and quality control monitoring to manage the workload effectively while maintaining quality.'
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Implement measures such as additional shifts, staff training, and quality control monitoring to manage the workload effectively while maintaining quality.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A chemical pathology lab receives updated guidelines for specimen handling and storage from a regulatory agency. How should the lab ensure that these guidelines are incorporated into its quality management system in compliance with ISO 15189 requirements?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Ignore the updated guidelines as they may require additional work.',
        'Incorporate the updated guidelines into laboratory procedures and document the changes.',
        'Implement the updated guidelines without proper documentation.',
        'Disregard the guidelines and continue with current practices.'
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Incorporate the updated guidelines into laboratory procedures and document the changes.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A chemical pathology lab identifies a need to improve its document control procedures to ensure the traceability and integrity of laboratory records. What steps should the lab take to implement effective document control measures aligned with ISO 15189 standards?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Develop a document control procedure and implement it without staff training.',
        'Update document control procedures only when mandated by external auditors.',
        'Train staff on document control procedures, establish version control, ensure access controls, and regularly review and update documents as needed.',
        'Ignore document control procedures as they are unnecessary.'
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Train staff on document control procedures, establish version control, ensure access controls, and regularly review and update documents as needed.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Following a major renovation of the laboratory facilities, a chemical pathology lab conducts a risk assessment to identify potential hazards and mitigate risks to staff and patients. How should the lab document and address the findings of the risk assessment according to ISO 15189 recommendations?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Ignore the findings of the risk assessment as they may require costly interventions.',
        'Document the findings of the risk assessment, implement measures to mitigate identified risks, and regularly review and update the risk assessment as needed.',
        'Conduct the risk assessment without documenting the findings.',
        'Disregard the risk assessment and continue operations as usual.'
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Document the findings of the risk assessment, implement measures to mitigate identified risks, and regularly review and update the risk assessment as needed.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A chemical pathology lab participates in an external proficiency testing program for a specific analyte. How should the lab analyze and respond to the proficiency testing results to ensure continuous improvement and compliance with ISO 15189 standards for quality management systems?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Ignore proficiency testing results as they are not indicative of lab performance.',
        'Review proficiency testing results, identify areas for improvement, and implement corrective actions to address any deficiencies.',
        'Fabricate proficiency testing results to maintain the appearance of compliance.',
        'Discontinue participation in proficiency testing to save costs.'
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Review proficiency testing results, identify areas for improvement, and implement corrective actions to address any deficiencies.',
    ),
  ]
};
